ILGWU New York Cloak Joint Board Minutes 5780/032
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Women's clothing industry--United States.; Women's clothing industry--New York (State)--New York.; Labor unions--Clothing workers--United States.; Labor unions--Clothing workers--New York (State)--New York.; Clothing workers--United States.; Clothing workers--New York (State)--New York.; Industrial relations--United States.; Industrial relations--New York (State)--New York.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. New York Joint Board of the Dressmakers' Union.
5457224
- Joint Board Minutes, 1926-1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Joint Board Minutes from January 6, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Joint Board Minutes, 1929-1931 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Joint Board Minutes, 1931-1933 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Joint Board Minutes, 1933-1936 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Joint Board Minutes, 1936-1939 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Joint Board Minutes, 1939-1942 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Joint Board Minutes, 1942-1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Joint Board Minutes, 1945-1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Joint Board Minutes, 1955-1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Joint Board Grievance Committee Minutes, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Joint Board Grievance Committee Minutes, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Joint Board Grievance Committee [cases 2400-2465], 1951-1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Joint Board Grievance Committee [cases 2466-2530], 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Joint Board Grievance Committee [cases 2531A-2591], 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Joint Board Grievance Committee [cases 2592-2677], 1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Joint Board Grievance Committee [cases 2678-2740], 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Joint Board Grievance Committee [cases 2741-2799], 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Joint Board Grievance Committee [cases 2800-2880], 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Joint Board Grievance Committee [cases 2881-2958], 1965-1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Joint Board Appeal Committee Minutes, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Joint Board Appeal Committee [cases 949-1006], 1956-1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1924-1927 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Russian
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1930-1934 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1935-1938 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1943-1949 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1944-1949 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Russian Polish Cloak Makers Union Minutes, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1948 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1944-1948 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1950 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1950 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1952 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1950-1952 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Retirement Fund Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1946-1950 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1946-1950 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1952 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1950-1952 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 1 of 3], 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 2 of 3], 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 3 of 3], 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 1 of 3], 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 2 of 3], 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 3 of 3], 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 1 of 3], 1958-1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 2 of 3], 1958-1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Pension Committee Minutes [folder 3 of 3], 1958-1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Executive Committee Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1943-1952 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Executive Committee Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1943-1952 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Executive Committee Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1952-1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Executive Committee Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1952-1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Monthly Financial Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1950 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Monthly Financial Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1944-1950 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Monthly Financial Reports [folder 1 of 3], 1951-1959 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Monthly Financial Reports [folder 2 of 3], 1951-1959 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Monthly Financial Reports [folder 3 of 3], 1951-1959 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Monthly Financial Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1964 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Monthly Financial Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1964 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Finance Committee [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1961 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Finance Committee [folder 2 of 2], 1944-1961 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Investment Committee Minutes, 1944-1951 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Investment Committee Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Investment Committee Minutes, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Investment Committee Minutes, 1952-1959 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Investment Committee Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1959 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Investment Committee Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1959 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Rules Committee Minutes, 1943-1954 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Rules Committee Minutes, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Rules Committee Minutes, 1956-1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Administrative Committee Minutes, 1944-1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Appeals Committee Minutes, 1946-1958 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Appeals Committee Minutes, 1958-1962 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Special Investigating Committee Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1952 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Special Investigating Committee Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1952 (Box 7, Folder 14)